Sleep Tight America. These Women Carry Guns.
Feds! is a comedy, crime film directed by Daniel Goldberg.
Ellie DeWitt and Janis Zuckermann are admitted to
the very strict FBI Training Academy.
They get a hard course, in which they learn to deal
with guns and to recognise crimes.
They also get a physical training.
It appears that Ellie is a real fighting- machine, in
contrast with Janis, the great student.
They have to help each other, all the way to graduation.
Ellis DeWitt, played by Rebecca De Mornay.
Janis Zuckerman, played by Mary Gross.
Bill Belecki, played by Fred Thompson.
Howard Butz, played by Larry Cedar.
Brent Sheppard, played by Ken Marshall.
George Hupperman, played by Raymond Singer.
Feds is a 1988 American crime comedy film co-written and directed by Dan
Goldberg, and starring Rebecca De Mornay and Mary Gross.
The plot follows two women, the ex-Marine Ellie and Bryn Mawr graduate Janis, who aim
to become FBI agents and enroll at the training center in Quantico.
The ending credits state that the real FBI did not support
the film or assist the production in any way.
The tone is lighthearted.